Muhammad Hafiz Bin Mohd Idris

🗣 Johor Bahru, Malaysia 🛮 codenamehafiz.@gmail.com 🔲 017-5420192 🕳 codenamehafiz.github.io

SUMMARY

Web developer with 7+ years of experience with some experience in mobile app development. I excel at creating responsive and user-friendly web applications, writing a clean code, optimizing application performance and collaborating with cross-functional teams. I am a self-motivated learner with a passion for staying up to date with the latest web technologies and industry trends.

EXPERIENCE

Front-End Developer

Cybersolution Technologies

December 2018 - Present, Johor Bahru, Johor

- Involved mainly in front-end development of government web applications based on projects each delivered by phase.
- Also involved in ad hoc backend changes that require to modify, fix or create APIs.
- Create working prototypes that users can interact and test before initializing development.
- Communicate with users to identify their needs, ensuring that solutions delivered met their requirement.
- Become the go-to person in the company for React applications and frontend development.
- Develop, test, plan and cooperate internally with team members in making sure the overall flow of the system meets the user needs.

Web Developer

GarGeon

May 2018 - November 2018, Johor Bahru, Johor

- A part of the leading team that decides the whole architecture of the company product.
- Involved in full-stack development of web and mobile application that attempt to tackle the problems in the waste industry.
- Directly collaborated with the founders and CEO ensuring that the project aligned with business goals and user needs.

Programmer

Zanko

September 2016 - February 2018, Johor Bahru, Johor

- Contribute in designing the UI of web application from scratch and create UI prototypes for the purpose of collecting user requirements.
- Assist in creating controllers and SQL queries that control the type of data that need to be displayed.
- Work with the team in ensuring that the system solution meets the user's needs and expectations.

Front-End Web Developer

Misa Travel

November 2015 - August 2016, Johor Bahru, Johor

- Participated in the development of Kiasu Perks, a mobile app that let users enjoy discounts and deals around the world.
- Tasked in the creation of the administrator web application dashboard where I designed the interface and integrate the front-end with the APIs given.
- Assisted in the creation of the mobile app's landing page and the mobile UI.

EDUCATION

Diploma in Information Technology

Kolej Poly-Tech MARA • Batu Pahat, Johor • 2015 • 3.62 CGPA

Malaysian Certificate of Education (SPM)

SMK Bandar Baru UDA • Johor Bahru, Johor • 2011

SKILLS

Technical Skills:

ReactJS, ExpressJS, AngularJS, JavaScript, TypeScript, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, GIT, Docker, PHP, Ionic, CodeIgniter, SQL, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe XD

Industry Knowledge:

Development Libraries And Framework, UI/UX, Testing, Debugging, Web Application Optimization, Artificial Intelligence